{
    "id": "a8b50f65134f4a09bb8696b3b2b95fc2",
    "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I wrote an essay today. / An essay .......................... by me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is written",
                "was written",
                "has written"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She gave the beggar a coin. / The beggar ........................ a coin.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is given",
                "was given",
                "has given"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You need sodium bicarbonate for this experiment. / Sodium bicarbonate ....................... for this experiment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is needing",
                "is needed",
                "is being needed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Bad people hurt good people. / Good people ....................... by bad people.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hurt",
                "are hurt",
                "have hurt"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Supriya took her mother to the hospital. / Supriya's mother ..................... to the hospital.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has taken",
                "was taken",
                "is taken"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She threw stones at the dog. / Stones ............................ at the dog.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are thrown",
                "were thrown",
                "have been thrown"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The masons are building the house. / The house ....................... by the masons.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is built",
                "is being built",
                "has been built"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am writing a novel. / A novel .............................. by me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is writing",
                "is written",
                "is being written"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She helped the boy. / The boy ............................... by her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has been helped",
                "was helped",
                "is helped"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She showed me the photograph. / I ........................... the photograph.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am shown",
                "have been shown",
                "was shown"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Cats chase mice. / Mice ......................... by cats.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "chased",
                "are chased",
                "have chased"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The pigeon does not make nests. / Nests ............................ by the pigeon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have not been made",
                "are not made",
                "were not made"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I donâ€™t know Michael. / Michael ............................ to me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is not known",
                "has not been known",
                "was not known"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}